bridgespan.org 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Bridgespan

#### Bridgespan is committed to your privacy

We’re dedicated to working in your best interests and to conforming with the latest U.S. and European privacy standards, including the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We want to be transparent in how and when we collect and use your data and to help you better understand how to control that data. 

In plain language, we collect some data about visitors and newsletter subscribers through forms and cookies (small tracking codes) on our site. We use this information to keep in touch with you (if you fill out a contact form or newsletter subscription request, for instance) and to improve the content we provide (by identifying what articles get the most attention and to fix site usability issues, for example). 

We don’t sell, rent, or otherwise share your personal data with anyone outside of Bridgespan except as necessary to provide a requested service (such as accepting payment for submitting a job posting) or to fulfill legal obligations in the interest of the safety of The Bridgespan Group, the users of our website, or the public.

Some of the tools on our site also collect information and use their own cookies in order to provide you with features and services, and you should review those companies’ privacy policies. These include our social sharing buttons ([AddThis](http://www.addthis.com/privacy)), our commenting feature ([Disqus](https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy)), and our online polling/feedback/user experience tool ([HotJar](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy)). We also use [Google Analytics](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en) to track overall activity on our site.

If you ever have any questions, suggestions or concerns about your data privacy, including requests to have your data removed, please send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a9cadcdaddc6c4ccdbdaccdbdfc0cacce9cbdbc0cdceccdad9c8c787c6dbce96dadccbc3cccadd94f9dbc0dfc8cad08c9b99f9c6c5c0cad08c9b99f8dcccdaddc0c6c7). You can also send letters to: The Bridgespan Group, 2 Copley Place, 7th Floor, Suite 3700b, Boston, MA, 02116

Read below for additional details about our policies and procedures. 

#### Further Details

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes the practices of The Bridgespan Group, Inc. ("Bridgespan") with respect to the gathering and use of personal information submitted to Bridgespan through the Bridgespan website (the "Bridgespan Site").  All capitalized terms not defined here, shall be given the same meaning as defined in the Bridgespan Group General Terms and Conditions ("Terms").

This Policy does not cover Bridgespan’s confidentiality and privacy obligations to the employers and search firms that submit job listings and related employment information to Bridgespan in connection with recruiting services. Such obligations are governed by a separate written agreement between each of the employers and search firms and Bridgespan. This Policy also does not apply to the practices of unrelated third-party service providers or companies accessed through links provided for your convenience from the Sites.

#### What information we collect

Bridgespan, or a service provider operating on Bridgespan's behalf, collects certain Nonpublic Personal Information ("NPI") which is submitted by you when you register as a User on the Sites. You may also submit NPI to Bridgespan when you apply through the Sites for a job opening at Bridgespan itself, or when you reply via the Sites to an employer that has posted a job on the Recruiting Platform. The NPI may include, but may not be limited to:

  * Your name
  * Name of employer
  * Home or office mailing address
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone, cellular and fax numbers
  * Credit card information (if applicable).

In addition, when you visit the Sites, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Sites. This information is gathered through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small data text file that a website server writes to your hard-drive when you visit the Sites. A cookie assigns a unique identification to your computer and may be used for security purposes, to facilitate transactions, to personalize the Sites, or to gather information about the visit.

#### When we disclose your nonpublic personal information

Bridgespan does not disclose NPI to any third party, except for the purposes of providing the Services to you, or as otherwise disclosed in this Policy. Specifically, we may share the NPI that we collect with the following entities:

  * To service providers with whom we subcontract, including those who host and maintain the Sites, fulfillment companies who distribute our materials or handle billing for certain services
  * If you apply for a job on the Recruiting Platform, to the employer or agency that advertises the job, and to third parties that may search our database of job applicants
  * To government agencies and law enforcement officials, when we are required to do so to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or when Bridgespan in its sole discretion, believes it is required or appropriate in order to comply with the law
  * We also reserve the right to disclose NPI in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Bridgespan's Terms and Conditions or other agreements, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. If Bridgespan merges with another organization, your NPI will be acquired by that organization.
  * For participants in the Leadership Accelerator program, see the program's Terms of Use.

#### Disclosures that you control

If you submit NPI, or other personal information not specifically listed here, to any of our Community Forums or other areas of the Sites that can be accessed by Users or others (such as in questions, comments, postings, listserves, email threads or other such places), then your submissions will be public, and Bridgespan’s privacy obligations will no longer apply. If you submit NPI directly to one of our service providers, then such submissions are governed by the received service provider's terms and privacy policy, and not Bridgespan's. Please check the Terms for more information on this subject under the section called "Your Submissions and Activities."

You should be aware that your User Name may be displayed throughout the Sites and therefore may be available to the public. All of your activities on the Sites may ultimately be traceable to your User Name. Other people can see your submissions and your postings to publicly-accessible sections of the Sites. Therefore, if you associate your given name with your User Name, people who know you will be able to identify your activities and comments on the Sites. Bridgespan is not responsible or liable for the consequences of this disclosure by you.

#### How we use your nonpublic personal information within Bridgespan

Bridgespan uses NPI collected from Users in order to administer the Services requested by you, to make the Sites more useful, to respond to your queries, and to inform Users of new products and services offered on the Sites. We also may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and administer the Sites.

Your Internet Protocol address and information regarding the web pages on the Sites that you visit, or that linked to the Sites, may also be used to gather broad demographic information, interests, and behavior so that we may better understand our Users. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve the Sites’ design and functionality. Bridgespan may share aggregated demographic, product usage, or traffic pattern information for marketing purposes with other organizations, but these statistics will include no NPI. Except as noted above, your NPI will not be shared with other organizations for marketing purposes without your consent.

#### Security

Although the Sites have security measures in place to protect against unauthorized access to and the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control, we cannot guarantee that such security measures will be sufficient, will not be breached, and that your NPI, Private Information, or other information may not be disclosed or otherwise accessed in an unauthorized manner. Certain information, including NPI and Private Information, may be transmitted by you and to you by unsecured electronic mail. Although it may be illegal to intercept or disclose these messages, these transmissions are not secured.

#### How to review and update your information

Bridgespan provides methods of updating your information and contact preferences. You may update your information and contact preferences online, or write, e-mail, or telephone us with changes to your information and contact preferences.

Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6f0c1a1c1b00020a1d1c0a1d19060c0a2f0d1d060b080a1c1f0e0141001d08501c1a0d050a0c1b523f1d06190e0c164a5d5f3f0003060c164a5d5f3e1a0a1c1b060001).

Physical address: The Bridgespan Group, 2 Copley Place, 7th Floor, Suite 3700b, Boston, MA, 02116

Phone: (617) 572-2833

#### Opt-out policy

You may at any time request not to be contacted by Bridgespan. "Opt out" requests should be sent to the address indicated on the materials sent by Bridgespan or by replying to the email in which such material was sent, or by telephone to Bridgespan Customer Service. Please note that Bridgespan Customer Service may ask you to follow up your request in writing, for our records.

#### Linked websites

The Sites provide hypertext links to and framed content from other websites that may be governed by privacy policies that are different from those provided herein. If you leave the Sites, or if you are presented with a framed web page that is branded with the marks of a third party, this Privacy Policy will not apply. You should read the privacy policies of websites reached through the use of links or reached through the interactions with framed content on the Sites. Bridgespan is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through those websites, and Bridgespan expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

#### Applicable laws

These Sites are published in the United States and is subject to laws of the United States. If you are located in a country outside the United States and voluntarily submit personal information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States.

#### Revisions to this policy

As the Sites grow and new features are added, or legal requirements change, this Privacy Policy may be amended by posting the amended Privacy Policy on the Sites. The amended Privacy Policy, which will apply to all NPI held by Bridgespan, will automatically be effective 30 days after it is initially posted on the Sites.

_Effective Date of Privacy Policy: May 24, 2018._

This work is licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).   
Permissions beyond the scope of this license are available in our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.bridgespan.org/about-us/terms-and-conditions).
